set the wrap style 2:No word wrapping
(menu - file - properties)
if you put the subs on Top of screen, set the vert margin more than 2.5 times as large as font size.
I wanna give it to you now
You're still doing well, right? (X2)
You were so special, woo woo woo woo
When you make a turn in the alley and enter
That kid might come out and surprise you
Who was glowing white in the dark night
And sparkled in the white snow
Maybe I, maybe I still
Love you The fluttering wishes, yeah
The confession that I never made, yeah
I will visit you with the white snow
and tell you, yeah I will tell you while looking at your eyes, yeah
The love that remains in me, yeah