I wonder when it was
itsukara darou
that your laughing voice grew far away
kimi no warau koe tooku
The end comes all too quickly
shiawase no owari nante
to happiness, doesn’t it?
akkenai mono da ne
The innumerable tears
kazoekirenai
and the listless tomorrow too
namida mo kedarui asu mo
All those words we traded
kawashita kotoba
won’t let them become memories
subete omoide ni wa sasenai
In order to bring back your smile
kimi no egao torimodosu tame
No matter how many times, I won’t stop singing
nando demo boku wa uta wo yamenai
I’ll pass a lifetime of nights
ikutsumo no yoru wo koe
Until the day my wish is granted
kono negai kanau sono hi made